1
00:00:00,590 --> 00:00:03,620
Hi, Carol! Where's Tom?
你好,Carol! Tom在哪儿?

2
00:00:04,090 --> 00:00:06,320
He's upstairs.
他在楼上.

3
00:00:06,320 --> 00:00:08,650
He's having a bath.
他正在洗澡.

4
00:00:08,650 --> 00:00:09,980
Tom!
Tom!

5
00:00:09,980 --> 00:00:11,530
Yes?
什么事?

6
00:00:11,590 --> 00:00:13,510
Sam's here.
Sam来了.

7
00:00:13,540 --> 00:00:15,970
I'm nearly ready.
我马上就好.

8
00:00:16,410 --> 00:00:17,930
Hello, Sam.
你好, Sam.

9
00:00:17,930 --> 00:00:19,720
Have a cigarette.
请抽烟.

10
00:00:19,720 --> 00:00:21,670
No, thanks, Tom.
不,谢谢, Tom.

11
00:00:21,670 --> 00:00:24,160
Have a glass of whisky then.
那么来杯威士忌吧.

12
00:00:24,160 --> 00:00:26,160
OK. Thanks.
好的,谢谢.

13
00:00:26,170 --> 00:00:28,510
Is dinner ready, Carol?
Carol,饭好了吗?

14
00:00:28,510 --> 00:00:30,850
It's nearly ready.
马上就好.

15
00:00:30,850 --> 00:00:34,850
We can have dinner at seven o'clock.
7点钟我们可以吃饭.

16
00:00:34,850 --> 00:00:38,430
Sam and I had lunch together today.
我和Sam今天一起吃的午饭.

17
00:00:38,440 --> 00:00:40,760
We went to a restaurant.
我们去了一家饭店.

18
00:00:40,760 --> 00:00:42,780
What did you have?
你们吃什么?

19
00:00:42,780 --> 00:00:46,300
We had roast beef and potatoes.
我们吃的是烤牛肉和土豆.

20
00:00:46,300 --> 00:00:47,870
Oh!
噢!

21
00:00:47,870 --> 00:00:50,120
What's the matter, Carol?
怎么了,Carol?

22
00:00:50,350 --> 00:00:53,160
Well, you're going to have
唉,今晚你们又要吃

23
00:00:53,160 --> 00:00:57,390
 roast beef and potatoes again tonight!
烤牛肉和土豆了!

