1
00:00:00,220 --> 00:00:01,940
Hello, Ken.

2
00:00:02,070 --> 00:00:03,870
Hi, George.

3
00:00:04,570 --> 00:00:07,620
Have you just been to the cinema?

4
00:00:07,620 --> 00:00:09,900
Yes, I have.

5
00:00:09,900 --> 00:00:11,420
What's on?

6
00:00:11,420 --> 00:00:13,750
'Paris in the spring'.

7
00:00:13,750 --> 00:00:16,940
Oh, I've already seen it.

8
00:00:16,940 --> 00:00:20,660
I saw it on television last year.

9
00:00:21,160 --> 00:00:24,990
It's an old film, but it's very good.

10
00:00:25,000 --> 00:00:28,170
Paris is a beautiful city.

11
00:00:28,170 --> 00:00:30,320
I've never been there.

12
00:00:30,530 --> 00:00:33,480
Have you ever been there, Ken?

13
00:00:33,490 --> 00:00:38,010
Yes, I have. I was there in April.

14
00:00:38,020 --> 00:00:41,100
Pairs in the spring, eh?

15
00:00:41,140 --> 00:00:43,020
It was spring,

16
00:00:43,030 --> 00:00:45,480
but the weather was awful.

17
00:00:45,480 --> 00:00:48,310
It rained all the time.

18
00:00:48,480 --> 00:00:51,160
Just like London!

