1
00:00:00,570 --> 00:00:03,090
Is my car ready yet?
我的汽车修好了吗?

2
00:00:03,090 --> 00:00:05,140
I don't know. sir.
我不知道,先生.

3
00:00:05,140 --> 00:00:07,920
What's the number of your car?
您的汽车牌号是多少?

4
00:00:07,920 --> 00:00:13,730
It is LFZ 312G.
是 LFZ312G.

5
00:00:13,730 --> 00:00:16,620
When did you bring it to us?
您什么时候送来的?

6
00:00:16,640 --> 00:00:20,310
I brought it here three days ago.
3天前.

7
00:00:20,310 --> 00:00:24,240
Ah, yes, I remember now.
啊,是的,我现在记起来了.

8
00:00:24,300 --> 00:00:27,530
Have your mechanics finished yet?
你们的机械师修好了吗?

9
00:00:27,530 --> 00:00:30,830
No, they're still working on it.
没有,他们还在修呢.

10
00:00:31,590 --> 00:00:36,690
Let's go into the garage and have a look at it.
我们到车库去看一下吧.

11
00:00:36,700 --> 00:00:39,140
Isn't that your car?
这难道不是您的车吗?

12
00:00:39,410 --> 00:00:43,140
Well, it was my car.
唔,这曾是我的车.

13
00:00:43,140 --> 00:00:45,760
Didn't you have a crash?
难说您没有出车祸吗?

14
00:00:45,800 --> 00:00:47,610
That's right.
是啊.

15
00:00:47,820 --> 00:00:51,360
I drove it into a lamp-post.
我把汽车撞在电线杆上了.

16
00:00:51,360 --> 00:00:54,570
Can your mechanics repair it?
你们的机械师能修好吗?

17
00:00:54,580 --> 00:00:58,390
Well, they're trying to repair it,sir.
啊,他们正设法修呢,先生.

18
00:00:58,400 --> 00:01:01,240
But to tell you the truth.
不过说实在的,

19
00:01:01,240 --> 00:01:03,790
you need a new car!
您需要一辆新车了!

