1
00:00:00,330 --> 00:00:04,290
Do you have any shoes like these?
像这样的鞋子你们有吗?

2
00:00:04,290 --> 00:00:05,880
What size?
什么尺码的?

3
00:00:06,060 --> 00:00:08,240
Size five.
5号的.

4
00:00:08,400 --> 00:00:09,870
what color?
什么颜色?

5
00:00:09,900 --> 00:00:11,760
Black.
黑的

6
00:00:12,130 --> 00:00:13,680
I'm sorry.
对不起,

7
00:00:13,680 --> 00:00:15,700
We don't have any.
我们没有.

8
00:00:16,210 --> 00:00:20,770
But my sister bought this pair last month.
但是,我姐姐上个月买了这双.

9
00:00:20,770 --> 00:00:23,220
Did she buy them here?
她是在这儿买的吗?

10
00:00:23,220 --> 00:00:27,910
No, she bought them in the U.S.
不.她是在美国买的.

11
00:00:28,130 --> 00:00:32,820
We had some shoes like those a month ago,
一个月前我们有这样的鞋,

12
00:00:32,820 --> 00:00:36,150
but we don't have any now.
但是现在没有了.

13
00:00:36,150 --> 00:00:39,980
Can you get a pair for me, please?
您能为我弄一双吗?

14
00:00:40,490 --> 00:00:43,640
I'm afraid that I can't.
恐怕不行.

15
00:00:43,990 --> 00:00:49,620
They were in fashion last year and the year before last.
这鞋在去年和前年流行,

16
00:00:49,630 --> 00:00:53,670
But they're not in fashion this year.
而今年已不流行了.

17
00:00:53,890 --> 00:00:57,490
These shoes are in fashion now.
现在流行的是这种鞋子.

18
00:00:57,570 --> 00:01:01,330
They look very uncomfortable.
这种鞋子看上去很不舒适.

19
00:01:01,700 --> 00:01:05,050
They are very uncomfortable.
的确很不舒适.

20
00:01:05,480 --> 00:01:10,220
But women always wear uncomfortable shoes!
可是女人们总是穿不舒适的鞋子!

