1
00:00:01,230 --> 00:00:04,330
Hello, Sam. Come in.
你好，萨姆。进来吧。

2
00:00:04,630 --> 00:00:06,060
Hi, Sam.
你好，萨姆。

3
00:00:06,060 --> 00:00:08,250
We're having lunch.
我们正在吃午饭，

4
00:00:08,520 --> 00:00:12,250
Do you want to have lunch with us?
你跟我们一起吃午饭好吗？

5
00:00:12,250 --> 00:00:14,610
No, thank you, Tom.
不，汤姆，谢谢。

6
00:00:14,610 --> 00:00:17,280
I've already had lunch.
我已经吃过饭了。

7
00:00:17,280 --> 00:00:21,110
I had lunch at half past twelve.
我在12点半吃的。

8
00:00:21,170 --> 00:00:24,330
Have a cup of coffee then.
那么喝杯咖啡吧。

9
00:00:24,330 --> 00:00:27,820
I've just had a cup, thank you.
我刚喝了一杯，谢谢。

10
00:00:28,050 --> 00:00:31,170
I had one after my lunch.
我是在饭后喝的。

11
00:00:31,170 --> 00:00:34,990
Let's go into the living room,Carol.
我们到客厅里去吧，卡罗尔。

12
00:00:34,990 --> 00:00:38,120
We can have our coffee there.
我们可以在那里喝咖啡。

13
00:00:38,360 --> 00:00:41,600
Excuse the mess, Sam.
屋子很乱，请原谅，萨姆。

14
00:00:41,700 --> 00:00:44,970
This room's very untidy.
房间里乱七八糟。

15
00:00:44,970 --> 00:00:48,060
We're packing our suitcases.
我们正在收拾手提箱。

16
00:00:48,070 --> 00:00:51,900
We're going to leave tomorrow.
明天我们就要走了。

17
00:00:52,080 --> 00:00:56,460
Tom and I are going to have a holiday.
我和汤姆准备去度假。

18
00:00:56,760 --> 00:00:59,130
Aren't you lucky!
你们真幸运！

19
00:00:59,610 --> 00:01:04,040
When are you going to have a holiday, Sam?
萨姆，你准备什么时候去度假？

20
00:01:04,040 --> 00:01:05,940
I don't know.
我不知道。

21
00:01:07,090 --> 00:01:11,200
I've already had my holiday this year.
今年我已度过假了。

22
00:01:11,200 --> 00:01:13,530
Where did you go?
你去哪儿了？

23
00:01:13,530 --> 00:01:15,560
I stayed at home!
我呆在这里了！

