1
00:00:00,720 --> 00:00:02,740
Good afternoon.
下午好.

2
00:00:03,300 --> 00:00:07,580
I believe that this house is for sale. 
我想这房子是要出售的吧!

3
00:00:07,580 --> 00:00:09,190
That's right.
是的.

4
00:00:09,280 --> 00:00:12,880
May I have a look at it, please?
我可以看一看吗?

5
00:00:13,380 --> 00:00:16,340
Yes, of course. Come in.
可以,当然可以.请进.

6
00:00:16,410 --> 00:00:19,580
How long have you lived here?
您在这里住了多长时间?

7
00:00:19,750 --> 00:00:23,080
I've live here for twenty years.
我在这里已经住了20年了.

8
00:00:23,680 --> 00:00:25,730
Twenty years!
20年!

9
00:00:25,730 --> 00:00:27,780
That's a long time.
这个时间可不短.

10
00:00:27,780 --> 00:00:32,610
Yes, I've been here since 1976.
是啊,从1976年起我就住在这里.

11
00:00:32,960 --> 00:00:36,750
Then why do you want to sell it?
那么,您为什么要卖掉它呢?

12
00:00:36,750 --> 00:00:39,570
Because I've just retired.
因为我刚退休.

13
00:00:39,720 --> 00:00:44,300
I want to buy a small house in the country.
我想在乡下买幢小房子.

14
00:00:44,690 --> 00:00:48,180
How much does this house cost?
这座房子卖多少钱?

15
00:00:48,190 --> 00:00:52,630
£68,500.
68,500英镑.

16
00:00:52,630 --> 00:00:55,180
That's a lot of money.
那可真是一大笔钱呢!

17
00:00:55,230 --> 00:00:58,440
It's worth every penny of it.
它确确实实值这么多钱.

18
00:00:58,680 --> 00:01:01,620
Well, I like the house,
啊,我喜欢这房子,

19
00:01:01,620 --> 00:01:04,580
but I can't decide yet.
但我还不能决定.

20
00:01:04,580 --> 00:01:08,000
My wife must see it first.
我妻子必须先来看一看.

21
00:01:08,260 --> 00:01:11,840
Women always have the last word.
女人总是最后说了算的.

