1
00:00:00,003 --> 00:00:00,820
Lesson 71  He's awful! 
他讨厌透了!

2
00:00:00,880 --> 00:00:04,500
What's Ron Marston like,Pauline?
Pauline,Ron Marston是怎样一个人?

3
00:00:04,500 --> 00:00:06,860
He's awful!
他讨厌透了!

4
00:00:07,420 --> 00:00:12,110
He telephoned me four times yesterday, 
他昨天给我打了4次电话,

5
00:00:12,720 --> 00:00:17,070
He telephoned the office yesterday morning 
他昨天上午和下午

6
00:00:17,070 --> 00:00:20,350
and yesterday afternoon.
把电话打到了我的办公室,

7
00:00:21,020 --> 00:00:24,480
My boss answered the telephone.
是我的老板接的.

8
00:00:24,930 --> 00:00:28,130
What did your boss say to him?
你老板是怎么对他说的?

9
00:00:28,130 --> 00:00:33,000
He said, 'Pauline is typing letters.
他说：“Pauline正在打信,

10
00:00:33,160 --> 00:00:36,410
She can't speak to you now!'
她现在不能同你讲话!”

11
00:00:36,950 --> 00:00:43,080
Then I arrived home at six o'clock yesterday evening.
后来,我昨晚6点钟回到家里.

12
00:00:43,090 --> 00:00:45,910
He telephoned again.
他又打来电话,

13
00:00:45,950 --> 00:00:49,330
But I didn't answer the phone!
但我没接.

14
00:00:49,330 --> 00:00:53,120
Did he telephone again last night?
他昨天夜里又打电话了吗?

15
00:00:53,120 --> 00:00:55,610
Yes, he did.
是的,打了.

16
00:00:55,610 --> 00:00:59,380
He telephoned at nine o'clock.
他在9点钟又打来了电话.

17
00:01:00,160 --> 00:01:02,770
What did you say to him?
你对他怎么说的?

18
00:01:03,160 --> 00:01:07,650
I said, 'This is Pauline's mother.
我说：“我是Pauline的母亲.

19
00:01:07,650 --> 00:01:12,340
Please don't telephone my daughter again!'
请不要再给我女儿打电话了!”

20
00:01:12,410 --> 00:01:15,190
Did he telephone again?
他又打了没有?

21
00:01:15,190 --> 00:01:18,180
No, he didn't!
没有!

