1
00:00:06,260 --> 00:00:09,175
5...4...3...
5...4...3...

2
00:00:11,048 --> 00:00:15,330
Sun Yu Chang is a member of the trade delegation now in Boston.
Sun Yu Chang是贸易代表团的一名成员  现在在波士顿.

3
00:00:15,334 --> 00:00:17,269
They've been talking to our governor.
他们在和我们州长进行会谈.

4
00:00:17,270 --> 00:00:19,494
How are the talks going,Mr.Chang?
会谈进展怎么样, Mr.Chang?

5
00:00:19,495 --> 00:00:21,374
Very,very well.
非常非常好.

6
00:00:21,455 --> 00:00:23,570
Can you tell us how well?
你能告诉我们有多好吗?

7
00:00:23,814 --> 00:00:26,223
It's a negotiation.
它是一个谈判.

8
00:00:26,224 --> 00:00:28,428
We don't agree on every point.
我们并不是每一个观点都一致.

9
00:00:28,499 --> 00:00:32,391
And we are dealing with issues that affect trade everywhere.
并且我们正在处理的问题 会影响各个地方的贸易.

10
00:00:32,440 --> 00:00:33,927
For instance?
例如?

11
00:00:33,928 --> 00:00:35,900
Inflation,of course.
通货膨胀, 当然.

12
00:00:35,901 --> 00:00:39,343
Here,compared with inflation in our country.
这里, 和我们国家的通货膨胀相比.

13
00:00:39,344 --> 00:00:41,576
Also employment.
还有 就业问题.

14
00:00:41,600 --> 00:00:46,653
How much of our workforce is involved in trade with your country.
有多少我们的劳动力参与到同你们国家的贸易中.

15
00:00:46,654 --> 00:00:48,907
These affect our discussions.
这些影响我们的讨论.

16
00:00:48,908 --> 00:00:50,985
Will there be a trade agreement?
将会形成一个贸易协议吗?

17
00:00:50,986 --> 00:00:54,588
Oh yes.We are making progress all the time.
Oh yes. 我们一直在取得进展.

18
00:00:54,835 --> 00:00:57,107
Thank you for speaking with us,Mr.Chang.
谢谢你和我们谈话, Mr.Chang.

19
00:00:57,108 --> 00:00:58,284
My pleasure.
我的荣幸.

20
00:00:58,285 --> 00:01:01,177
Sun Yu Chang,ending on a positive note.
Sun Yu Chang, 结束在一个积极的音符上.

21
00:01:01,178 --> 00:01:04,687
This is Heather Vialo reporting live from the Sheraton Boston,
这里是Heather Vialo现场直播  来自Sheraton Boston

22
00:01:04,688 --> 00:01:06,323
for the Business Network.
为商业网络.

23
00:01:07,712 --> 00:01:09,501
OK.We're all set.
OK. 我们完成了.

24
00:01:09,792 --> 00:01:11,080
Thank you ,Mr.Chang.
谢谢你, Mr.Chang.


