1
00:00:07,774 --> 00:00:10,100
You would not believe  what just happened to me.
你肯定不会相信 刚刚在我身上发生了什么事

2
00:00:10,101 --> 00:00:12,058
Wendy!Are you all right?
Wendy! 你没事吧?

3
00:00:12,059 --> 00:00:13,564
Picture this,OK? 
想象一下这个, OK? 

4
00:00:13,565 --> 00:00:15,012
I'm on my way to work.
我在去上班的路上.

5
00:00:15,013 --> 00:00:16,376
I'm waiting in the subway.
正在等地铁.

6
00:00:16,377 --> 00:00:19,018
The train pulls in,the doors open.
列车开过来了, 门打开了.

7
00:00:19,019 --> 00:00:21,264
But it's packed.People can't get in.
但非常拥挤. 人们进不去.

8
00:00:21,265 --> 00:00:22,723
I see a little space.
我看到一点点空隙.

9
00:00:22,724 --> 00:00:24,759
So I swing my bag in front of me,
So 我把我的包放在我的前面, 

10
00:00:24,760 --> 00:00:26,027
to get on the train.
为了上车.

11
00:00:26,028 --> 00:00:28,608
And the doors shut!On the straps!
突然门关上了! 夹住了包的带子!

12
00:00:28,609 --> 00:00:30,724
Bam! And they don't open.
Bam! 它们不开了!

13
00:00:30,725 --> 00:00:31,958
Oh no.
Oh no.

14
00:00:31,959 --> 00:00:34,509
The people right inside the car see this,
车厢里的人们看到了这个,

15
00:00:34,510 --> 00:00:36,492
and start to shout at the conductor.
并且开始大声叫列车员.

16
00:00:36,493 --> 00:00:37,704
He doesn't hear them.
他没有听到这些.

17
00:00:37,705 --> 00:00:38,506
Meanwhile,
同时, 

18
00:00:38,507 --> 00:00:40,958
I'm beating on the door and shouting.
我拼命敲门和叫喊.

19
00:00:40,959 --> 00:00:42,773
The train leaves.
列车开走了.

20
00:00:42,774 --> 00:00:44,227
You're joking.
你在开玩笑.

21
00:00:44,546 --> 00:00:46,127
The train leaves,
列车开走了, 

22
00:00:46,128 --> 00:00:48,383
and takes my pocketbook with it.
还带走了我的钱包.

23
00:00:48,384 --> 00:00:50,771
There it goes. Down the track.
就那么走了. 沿着轨道.

24
00:00:50,790 --> 00:00:52,351
Unbelievable.
难以置信.

25
00:00:53,094 --> 00:00:54,533
Well, then what happened?
Well, 后来发生了什么?

26
00:00:54,534 --> 00:00:55,504
Thank goodness,
谢天谢地,

27
00:00:55,505 --> 00:00:58,077
someone turned my bag in  at the Lost and Found.
有人返还了我的包 在失物招领处.

28
00:00:58,078 --> 00:00:59,132
Do you believe it? 
你相信吗? 

29
00:00:59,133 --> 00:01:00,719
Mugged by a train!
被列车抢劫了!

30
00:01:01,513 --> 00:01:03,194
That's city life for you.
那就是你的城市生活.


