1
00:00:10,300 --> 00:00:13,593
Hey,Carl.Here's a postcard from Nina.
Hey,Carl. 这是一张明信片 来自于Nina.

2
00:00:13,779 --> 00:00:14,717
From Prague.
来自于布拉格.

3
00:00:15,212 --> 00:00:17,187
I saw Nina here two minutes ago.
我看到Nina在这儿 两分钟前.

4
00:00:17,328 --> 00:00:18,969
Oh,they've been back for days.
Oh, 她们已经回来好几天了.

5
00:00:19,226 --> 00:00:22,837
She writes,"I miss my baby,but I'm glad I'm here."
她写道, "我想念我的孩子, 但是我很高兴我在这里."

6
00:00:23,393 --> 00:00:24,544
What else?
还有什么?

7
00:00:24,687 --> 00:00:26,289
She says they've just arrived.
她说她们刚刚到达.

8
00:00:26,410 --> 00:00:28,884
Boy,this took a long time to get here.
Boy,这个花了很长时间才寄到.

9
00:00:29,005 --> 00:00:32,020
She says it's beautiful and she's already in love with the city.
她说那儿很美 并且她已经爱上了那座城市.

10
00:00:32,263 --> 00:00:33,403
I've never been.
我从来没去过.

11
00:00:33,611 --> 00:00:35,653
Me,neither.She makes it sound great.
我也没有. 她让那里听起来很棒.

12
00:00:36,235 --> 00:00:37,911
She said they had done a lot of walking.
她说她们做了许多步行.

13
00:00:38,035 --> 00:00:40,866
And she was going to do a lot more walking when she got back.
并且她打算做更多步行 在她回来之后.

14
00:00:41,546 --> 00:00:45,147
Let's see.It's a funny thing about travel.
咱们看看, 它是件奇怪的事情 关于旅行.

15
00:00:45,339 --> 00:00:46,258
What?
什么?

16
00:00:46,401 --> 00:00:48,858
People go all that way,to a completely new place.
人们走那么远, 到一个完全陌生的地方.

17
00:00:49,436 --> 00:00:51,477
They see their lives from a new perspective,
他们从一个新的角度去看他们的生活.

18
00:00:51,610 --> 00:00:52,739
-you know?   -Sure
-你知道吗?   -当然

19
00:00:52,880 --> 00:00:54,479
And they make decisions...
并且他们做决定…

20
00:00:54,618 --> 00:00:56,735
like they're going to do a lot more walking.
像他们将做更多步行

21
00:00:57,613 --> 00:00:58,870
Travel's a funny thing.
旅行是件有趣的事.

22
00:01:00,772 --> 00:01:02,145
Have a good trip,sir.
祝你旅途愉快, 先生.

