1
00:00:06,156 --> 00:00:08,160
George!What are you doing?
George! 你在干什么?

2
00:00:08,579 --> 00:00:09,672
I'm working.
我正在工作.

3
00:00:09,673 --> 00:00:10,984
Don't you hear the alarm?
你没有听到警报吗?

4
00:00:10,985 --> 00:00:12,199
Yes.It's horrible.
Yes. 烦死人了.

5
00:00:12,200 --> 00:00:13,692
Is there any way we can turn it off?
有什么方法 我们能关掉它吗?

6
00:00:13,693 --> 00:00:14,994
Turn it off?
把它关掉?

7
00:00:14,995 --> 00:00:16,469
It's just a drill.
只是个演习.

8
00:00:16,470 --> 00:00:18,375
George,it is an emergency drill.
George, 这是应急演习.

9
00:00:18,376 --> 00:00:20,281
It's important.
这是很重要的.

10
00:00:20,446 --> 00:00:22,092
What do I have to do?
我需要干什么?

11
00:00:22,262 --> 00:00:23,840
It's all here.
都在这儿.

12
00:00:23,841 --> 00:00:25,534
Read the instructions. 
读一下须知.

13
00:00:25,759 --> 00:00:29,752
If you discover a fire,call 911.
如果你发现着火, 拨打911.

14
00:00:29,753 --> 00:00:33,554
Give the address. Boston Sheraton Hotel,
提供地址. Boston Sheraton酒店.

15
00:00:33,555 --> 00:00:35,614
39 Dalton Street. 
多尔顿(Dalton) 街39号.

16
00:00:35,615 --> 00:00:36,927
They discovered the fire,NuLa.
他们发现火情了, NuLa.

17
00:00:36,928 --> 00:00:39,410
The alarm's already on.What else?
警报已经拉响了. 还有什么?

18
00:00:39,411 --> 00:00:42,535
Don't panic!Shut any open windows.
不要惊慌! 关上任何打开的窗子.

19
00:00:42,536 --> 00:00:44,650
Leave your office.
离开你的办公室.

20
00:00:44,752 --> 00:00:47,553
Shut all the doors behind you.
关上你身后所有的门.

21
00:00:54,272 --> 00:00:56,359
Go to your nearest exit.
去距离你最近的出口.

22
00:00:56,524 --> 00:00:58,315
Do not use the elevator.
不要使用电梯. 

23
00:00:58,316 --> 00:00:59,941
Use the stairs.
使用楼梯.

24
00:01:04,657 --> 00:01:05,955
Leave the building.
离开大楼.

25
00:01:05,956 --> 00:01:08,281
Women and children first.
妇女和儿童先走.

26
00:01:08,800 --> 00:01:11,047
It doesn't say that.
它没有说那个.


