1
00:00:07,314 --> 00:00:09,988
He's been fabulous.We'll miss him a lot.
他很出色. 我们会很想念他的.

2
00:00:10,133 --> 00:00:11,579
Will you get a new intern?
你会请一位新的实习生吗?

3
00:00:11,725 --> 00:00:14,697
Yes,but we'll need two new ones to replace Dean.
Yes,但是我们会需要两位新实习生来代替 Dean.

4
00:00:14,829 --> 00:00:17,116
I think we should just hire him when he graduates.
我认为我们应该就雇用他 当他毕业后.

5
00:00:17,242 --> 00:00:18,174
Maybe we will.
或许我们会的.

6
00:00:36,123 --> 00:00:37,453
What's in the box,NuLa?
这个盒子里是什么, NuLa?

7
00:00:37,628 --> 00:00:38,880
A portable CD player.
一个便携式的CD播放器.

8
00:00:39,082 --> 00:00:41,559
Oh,is that what we chipped in for?Great.
Oh, 那就是我们凑份子买的是吗?太好了.

9
00:00:42,223 --> 00:00:43,395
I have something else.
我有别的东西.

10
00:00:43,532 --> 00:00:44,405
What is it?
它是什么?

11
00:00:44,554 --> 00:00:46,315
A soccer ball.From Kevin and me.
一个足球. 来自Kevin和我.

12
00:00:46,458 --> 00:00:48,688
Oh Dean will like that.
Oh Dean会喜欢那个的.

13
00:00:49,446 --> 00:00:50,963
He'll come to his senses some day.
他会醒悟的 某天.

14
00:00:57,965 --> 00:01:01,150
Jarmusch,if I gain one ounce from this cake,I will kill you .
Jarmusch, 如果我长胖1盎司  吃了这个蛋糕后, 我会杀了你.

15
00:01:22,388 --> 00:01:23,795
They're right behind us.
他们就在我们后面.

16
00:01:42,829 --> 00:01:46,477
Kevin.You can't afford to take us to this restaurant.
Kevin. 你负担不起 带我们到这个餐厅.

17
00:01:46,656 --> 00:01:48,611
For a friend like you,Dean?
为了一个你这样朋友, Dean?

18
00:01:48,759 --> 00:01:50,105
Don't think anything of it.
小意思.

19
00:01:57,751 --> 00:01:59,733
Surprise!
没想到吧!


